quantumincomemachine.com 2016-05-05

# Quantum Income Machine

We maintain this page to demonstrate our firm commitment to the rights and privacy of our users. This page explains how our site collects information from our users and members and how it may be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding our users' personal data and how we may treat it.

**Information we may collect**  
We may collect information that our users provide to us when they make enquiries, buy things or complete a form on our site. We may also record details of our users' visits to our site and the resources that they access.

**IP addresses and cookies**  
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us do various things including storing information about your preferences (which allows us to customise our site according to your individual interests); speeding up your searches and recognising you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

**The free newsletter and mailing list**  
Upon confirmation that you would like to join our newsletter, we will from time to time send you free information relating to the products we market, general advice related to online marketing, and promotional material for other products.  
You may unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.

**Purchase agreement**  
When you sign up, we collect your name, phone number and e-mail address and may use this with a small number of third parties who we are working closely with. In particular, we may share your data with coaching partners who offer a related service to our own (where you have agreed to this).

**How we use your information**  
• To provide you with information, products or services (and updates to our service) that you request from us or which we feel may interest you and to carry out our obligations to you.

**Disclosure of your information**  
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985 or our associated companies.

**Where we store your personal data**  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Your rights**  
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.

You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Access to information**  
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**Changes to our privacy policy**  
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail
